Okay.
Balloon dog with a tail facing the left.
Yeah.
Uh, the music stand.
The music stand.
Or, yeah, it has a rectangle at the bottom.
Oh, okay.
It looks like a Nessie too, actually.
Uh, rectangle at the bottom.
It's a stick chunk, yeah.
Looks like a dinosaur to me now.
Okay, what's this?
Uh, this is the flat dog.
The dog standing flat to the left.
Is the kind of like long one?
Yeah, the wiener dog.
Okay.
Yeah.
Cool.
Oh, wiener dog.
Uh, the house with the extra roof thing, triangle.
Mushroom house.
Oh, okay.
Uh, the ballet dancer facing the right.
Uh, yeah.
Stretched out, weirdly.
Right.
Uh, sad boy.
Uh.
Sitting facing left.
Uh-oh.
This is okay.
We all know this is a sad boy.
Uh, the, like, guy kicking up with two triangles as legs.
Facing the left.
Also, like, two triangle legs all the way up the top.
It kind of looks like bunny ears at the top.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, we can just do bunny ears for this.
I don't think there's anything else.
Bunny ears at the top?
Okay.
Yeah, two triangles.
It's like a bunny drinking tea.
Yeah.
Uh, the cashier registrar thing.
Uh-huh.
Uh, guy also kind of dancing, but then extending a leg out, like, a triangle at the bottom.
And then a weird, like, trapezoid sticking out of his other side, left side.
Oh, like, towards the lower right?
Yeah.
I don't know what this, this is also a dancer guy.
Yeah, I think this one.
It's like a Turkish dancer.
Yeah, I think this is a Turkish dancer.
Okay, guy kicking, back kick.
Ah, yeah.
Uh, dog riding a dog.
Uh, okay.
Um, guy with a bull facing the right, but, like, uh, knees bent a little bit.
Oh, I see it.
Uh, bunny reading a book, like, kind of looking down or holding a diamond facing the left.
Oh, oh, oh, right.
Yeah, a triangular.
Basically all the triangle guys are bunnies.
This one.
Yeah.
Uh, sunglasses.
Sunglasses?
Yeah.
Okay, I got it.
Uh, regular house.
Uh, kneeling the guy.
Uh, just like, just kneeling to the right.
Oh, okay, like, no legs, no arms.
Yeah.
Okay.
The blob.
Uh, the waiter guy, like, holding something on a towel to the left.
Yeah.
Uh, traffic light.
Oh, okay.
Yay.
Okay.
Good.